We are weak.
There is an overwhelming
difference in fighting ability
between us and the evil gatherers.
But we must not give up!
Our goals are not the same as other groups.
We are here to collect the coins,
negotiate with the alien,
and put an end to this silly game.
We need every last ally we can find.
Hold on.
Can we really trust her?
What if she's dangerous, she--
Let me introduce you...
...to our new member.
"A few days earlier"
Who the hell are you?
How did you get my phone number?
You were being blackmailed
by a monster named Sudo, weren't you?
Are you one of his friends?
No.
I'm on your side.
Hang on, I've got something I think you'll like.
I'm going to hang up for a second.
What do you want?
Well... If possible,
I'd like to join your group.
Okay. Got it.
How did it go?
We're going to join these guys?
Right.
I don't know what their goal
is in gathering the coins.
But I want information.
Did you tell them about Sanbe?
No.
Why?
I asked him directly.
I vowed to help you two
after I witnessed your strength.
I will lay my life on
the line for you and Shuichi,
but I have no reason to help some random group.
That's great, huh?
He seems to like you quite a bit.
It suits me fine.
Anyhow, right now I just want some
pieces to move around the board.
And that's what I need them for.
Clair, do you think your sister is there?
Up in the mountains?
Yes, I do.
And I think she has allies, too.
She was speaking with someone on the phone.
Your sister said she was the one
that turned me into a monster.
She also said that she was supposed
to be the one inside me.
What did she mean by that?
What is she trying to do?
Do you really think you and I
met by coincidence?
It's not a coincidence. Remember what I said?
"We were brought together by destiny."
Thank you for coming.
All right then, mind going
back to your normal form?
Uhh!
What are you talking about?
You never mentioned this.
Everyone that joins our group
must enter into a special pact.
A special pact?
To complete it, we'll need you
to return to your normal form, for now.
If you don't want to, that's fine.
But you can't join us.
Let me think about it.
What'll we do, Clair?
Hold on, Shuichi.
But--
I told you!
What the hell is she doing?
Okay. I will enter the pact.
But I am the only one who will do so.
The only one?
Unlike all of you,
I don't have a secret to hide.
And my normal life isn't at
risk of being destroyed at this point.
Someone's coming out!
What the...?
By the way, I'm a normal human.
The gatherer is this costume.
They change into a costume
and put someone inside?
How strange, I've never
seen one like that before.
For now, I will enter your "pact."
If you are trustworthy, I will have
this boy enter the pact, too.
Can a normal human enter the pact, too?
That's fine. Follow me.
Clair! It's okay, I'll go too--
Sorry. Just leave it to me. Please.
Some people stay the same
when they transform, huh? I didn't know.
Why do you think so?
Because you're wearing a mask. Others were too.
One had a helmet. Another was wearing a sheet.
It's to hide their faces, right?
One wasn't hiding his face though.
That's right. He looked that
way after transforming, huh?
I bet he's just some ugly guy that
transforms into someone handsome.
Oh...
Can... Can I pet you?
Huh?
So... How does this pact work?
We make you vow to protect our secret.
I already heard that.
What exactly am I supposed to do...?
What exactly? Well... To put it simply...
I have the power to make people keep secrets.
Yoshioka! Stay away from him!
What are you freaking out about?
I'm sure it's fine, he looks pretty silly.
Plus you're the one that brought them here!
Go ahead.
Yay!
How cute! It's so soft...
What is she doing? How am I supposed to react?
Just as I thought. You're a very kind person.
To tell the truth...
I can understand animals' feelings.
Uh... I'm a human.
Honestly, I don't trust you.
What a mean thing to say.
You wanted to join us, after all.
You told me I was going
to enter a pact to keep secrets.
Also, why did you take off your clothes?
Don't worry about it.
An outsider was able to force their way in--
Can you say for sure
that your secret is still safe?
If I was one of those evil gatherers,
you'd all be dead already.
You aren't actually an
acquaintance of Ikeuchi's, are you?
What did you do to him?
Did you blackmail him?
Did you blackmail him into bringing you here?
That's my secret.
But you don't know how many of us
there are or what kind of powers we have.
Do you want to start a fight
with a group you know so little about?
What if Ikeuchi told me
what powers you all have?
That's not possible.
I know, because he's still alive.
You mean he'll die if he reveals your secrets?
I hate people that don't keep secrets.
Anyway, you're the one who's hard to trust.
You're not a gatherer--
why are you collecting coins?
How does getting close
to us fit in to your plot?
Well, fine, it's not like
it's something to hide.
Do you mind if I go get my phone?
Go ahead.
--You're so cute cute cute cute cute...
--Uh... Could you...?
...cute cute cute cute cute cute cute--
Clair! Did you finish the pact?
Not yet. Could you give me my phone?
Oh... Okay.
Thanks.
We're looking for her.
She's a monster, like you guys.
She killed my parents and
turned the boy with me into a monster.
I'm going to find her, and--
This is Elena Aoki, isn't it?
You know my sister?!
I see. You're Elena's younger sister.
I guess there is some resemblance.
You've got to tell me!
Is she in these mountains?
Why is she--
Well, then... I can tell you.
You're very clever.
And you're not shaken easily.
Not to mention being beautiful...
If you join us, I will tell you.
Okay.
All right, I will begin the ceremony.
Please lie down.
You don't really look any different
from a normal human.
And with your power to make people keep secrets,
you're unlike any monster I've faced before.
Not everyone has some kind of complex
in regards to their appearance.
Suffering from the spirit,
from relationships, is much more common.
I was in love with someone.
They were a teacher.
That person had had a strong moral compass--
they were troubled by our relationship
and eventually withdrew from me.
I was a fool--I talked
to my best friend about it,
thinking I could trust her to keep our secret.
I hate people that can't keep secrets.
Can I ask you a question?
Was that teacher a man? Or a woman?
She was a woman.
Wow, that's cool!
So with your nose, you can
pick up any scent? Like a dog?
Yeah.
Animals sure are incredible!
Like I said, I'm a human.
It's been a while since they went back there.
What exactly do you do for this pact?
I'm sorry, I can't say. That would
be giving away my friend's secret.
I'm happy to answer any questions
you have about me though.
Talking about yourself
doesn't count as revealing a secret!
Oh, uh... So, why did you
decide to start gathering coins?
Hmm... I'm not interested in the amazing
powers that the alien talks about, of course.
But if that power ends up in the hands
of someone who really wants it,
I'd be worried about what'd happen
to my school and my family.
It was scary to think about--
I had to do something about it.
That's weird, huh? A weak coward like me...
She is the same as me.
She knows how weak she is,
but she can't abandon others.
She seems to be having a lot of fun.
So, you said you have a
really good sense of smell, right?
Can it help you find things you lost?
I think so, if I know what it smells like.
I actually kind of lost
my wallet in the mountains here...
Did it have your ID in it or anything?
Yeah, it did. So if a bad person finds it...
Hey, are you okay?
Sorry, I don't have much stamina
even when I transform.
Huh? Are you transformed right now?
You don't seem any different
from a normal person...
I'm a little different. Don't laugh, okay?
Ooh! Weirdo!
No, it's not like that!
I just like animals, that's all.
I want to be a vet when I get older!
That's why I wanted to
be able to understand them,
but I never actually wanted to be one myself!
That alien was just having fun at my expense!
Okay! But I'm going
to look for your wallet alone.
That's no good! It's my wallet, after all!
Watch this.
I'll be able to find the wallet
more quickly alone.
I've got to hurry and
find it before someone else does.
Plus, if you come along,
your scent will throw me off track.
Well, what if I went inside you?
What?!
Well, if I'm inside
my scent won't get out, right?
And if I'm in there, I won't slow you down.
No, we can't do that!
Why not? Will she--
will your girlfriend get mad?
No! I mean, Clair isn't
my girlfriend or anything!
But your clothes will get dirty, and, uh--
Then I'll take them off!
Wait--
Stop that!
Please let me in!
Yoshioka...
Is this where you get in?
Yeah, but... stop!
I'm going in.
Hang on!
Don't move. This is the best option we have.
Are you going to leave me behind in the forest?
Ok, here I go.
Yoshioka...!
S-Stop!
Stop, please!
So, what do I do?
Just try moving slowly to start.
Okay.
I'm sorry! It doesn't feel like my body.
Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine, just calm down.
I'll move, you can just sit there.
It's not like it was with Clair.
It was so easy for her, from the start.
You're thinking about her now, aren't you?
Somehow, I can sense your feelings.
Yeah, when you think of her, it's--
No! You've got it wrong...
So... Is this part of the "ceremony"?
It's not as though I don't like people like you.
Love takes many forms...
But I don't think we know
each other well enough for this.
I apologize.
That was close!
All right, I'll begin the official ceremony.
This is a choker woven from my hair.
I'm going to wrap it around your neck.
Don't worry. It'll meld with your body,
and nobody will be able to see it.
However, it will still be there.
So? How does it protect your secrets?
It's simple.
If you reveal our secrets
or somehow feel yourself
that you've betrayed us,
the choker will respond to your feelings
and cut your head off.
Your power is so specific--not like
any of the other monsters I've seen.
The difference is that I had
a clear vision of what I wanted.
Those without a clear vision
transform into something
that can grant their subconscious wishes.
I actually listened to what the alien said--
I formed a vision, told him what I wanted,
and this is how I transformed.
To make those who reveal secrets
pay for what they've done.
Just to make sure... You do have
information on my sister, right?
Yeah.
All right. Go ahead, then.
I'll put your clothes in the helmet
and hide them, for now.
If we take them with us,
the scent will get in the way.
Huh?
What?! Underwear?!
Are you completely naked in there?!
B-But you said my clothes would get dirty!
A-Are you dumb?!
I'm not dumb! It's just a crazy situation, okay?
You're the one who feels happy about it!
I'm not happy!
Yes, you are! I can sense your feelings!
Let's stop messing around,
we need to find your wallet.
Okay.
What are you doing, Subaru?
I just found this wallet. Must be my lucky day.
"Episode 7: Metamorphosis"